A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Publications, Working Files and Photographs FA1394
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Publications - Working Files, 1973-2001; 1; 19.44 Cubic Feet 50 containers
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Good Neighbor, Foundation-wide, Publications and Media, Master Grants List, 2001 January (Box 33, Folder 331)
  - Master Grants List 2000 - Assets, 2001 January (Box 33, Folder 332)
  - Master Grants List 2000 for Website - Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), 2001 January (Box 33, Folder 333)
  - Master Grants List 2000 - Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Governance and Civil Society (GCS), 2001 January (Box 33, Folder 334)
  - Master Grants List 2000 - Education, Media, Arts, and Culture - Education, Knowledge and Religion, 2001 January (Box 34, Folder 335)
  - Master Grants List 2000 - Media, Arts, and Culture, 2001 November (Box 34, Folder 336)
  - Master Grants List 2000 - Foundation-wide Actions, Good Neighbor, 2001 January (Box 34, Folder 337)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Assets, 2001 January (Box 34, Folder 338)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Peace and Social Justice, 2001 January (Box 34, Folder 339)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Education, Media, Arts and Culture, 2001 January (Box 34, Folder 340)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Assets, 2001 January (Box 34, Folder 341)
  - 2000 Master Grants List for Web Site - Education, Media, Arts and Culture, 2001 January (Box 34, Folder 342)
  - 2000 Master Grants List for Web Site - Peace and Social Justice, Good Neighbor, Foundation-wide Actions, 2001 January (Box 34, Folder 343)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List, OS Edits - Assets, 2001 February (Box 34, Folder 344)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Peace and Social Justice, 2001 February (Box 34, Folder 345)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - EMAC, Good Neighbor Grants, and Foundation-wide Actions, 2001 February (Box 34, Folder 346)
  - Master Grants List 2000 - Assets, 2001 March (Box 34, Folder 347)
  - Master Grants List 2000 - Peace and Social Justice, 2001 March (Box 35, Folder 348)
  - Master Grants List 2000 - EMAC, 2001 March (Box 35, Folder 349)
  - 2000 Annual Report - Publications and Other Media, Selected Books, Articles and Reports List, 2001 February (Box 35, Folder 350)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Assets, 2001 February (Box 35, Folder 351)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Peace and Social Justice, 2001 January (Box 35, Folder 352)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - EMAC, 2001 February (Box 35, Folder 353)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Good Neighbor Grants and Foundation-wide Actions, 2001 February (Box 35, Folder 354)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Assets, 2001 February (Box 35, Folder 355)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Peace and Social Justice, 2001 February (Box 35, Folder 356)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - EMAC, 2001 February (Box 35, Folder 357)
  - 2000 Annual Report Grants List - Good Neighbor Grants, Foundation-wide Actions, Other Grants (Delegated-Authority Grants and Foundation-Administered Projects), 2001 February (Box 35, Folder 358)
  - 2000 Annual Report Split Grants, 2001 January (Box 35, Folder 359)
  - Individual Grants List (3 folders), 2000 (Box 36, Folder 360-362)
  - Ford Foundation Style Guide Drafts with Edits (3 folders), 1992 (Box 36, Folder 363-365)
  - Ford Foundation Style Guide: FF-STYL.HPL, Word Perfect 5.1, Alice Tufel, 1992 May 8; 3 1/2 inch floppy disk (Box 36, Folder 365)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    From original envelope, "This disk has the original document with changes. There is no other copy on the system or on a disk."
  - Changing Relations: Newcomers and Established Residents in U.S. Communities - Print Quotations (3 folders), 1993 February (Box 36, Folder 366-368)
  - Summer Report 1993 Production File (2 folders), 1993 June (Box 36, Folder 369-370)
  - 1991 Annual Report - Photo Comps (Box 37, Folder 371)
  - 1991 Annual Report Covers (Box 37, Folder 372)
  - Annual Report Paper, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 373)
  - 1991 Annual Report Paper Quotations, 1992 February (Box 37, Folder 374)
  - 1991 Annual Report Typesetting Quotations, 1992 February (Box 37, Folder 375)
  - Ford Foundation 1991 Annual Report - Charts and Maps, FreeHand 3.0, 1992 February; 3 1/2 inch floppy disk (Box 37, Folder 375)
  - Ford Foundation 1991 Annual Report - Investments and Expenses Revised, 1992 February; 3 1/2 inch floppy disk (Box 37, Folder 375)
  - Printed Supplies, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 376)
  - Ford Foundation Annual Report 1991 - Manuscripts (3 folders), 1992 February (Box 37, Folder 377-379)
  - Program-Related Investments reports (2 folders), undated (Box 37, Folder 380, Box 38, Folder 381)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Photocopies of Photographs (Box 38, Folder 382)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Photographers (2 folders) (Box 38, Folder 383-384)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Schedules, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 385)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 386)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Memos, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 387)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Exhibit, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 388)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Working Draft, 1992 September (Box 38, Folder 389)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Invitations (Box 38, Folder 390)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Maps and Proposal Ad Layout (Box 38, Folder 391)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Program Book - Design Layouts (Box 38, Folder 392)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Posters (Box 38, Folder 393)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Semi-Finalists (Box 38, Folder 394)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Program Book - Quotations (Box 38, Folder 395)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Program Book - Manuscripts (3 folders) (Box 39, Folder 396-398)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Slide Show (Box 39, Folder 399)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1992 - Slide Show (4 folders) (Box 39, Folder 400-403)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Program Book - Manuscript (2 folders) (Box 39, Folder 404-405)
    Innovations in State and Local Government Awards Program - Update 1990: A Report to the National Advisory Committee, Information on 1991 Finalists and Previous Award Winners, Finalists' Presentations Schedule, press releases, 1991 Program Book
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Program Book - Dummies (Box 39, Folder 406)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Press Release Drafts - The Award Recipients (Box 40, Folder 407)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Awards Brochure Specs (Box 40, Folder 408)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Meeting (Box 40, Folder 409)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Program Book - Design/Layouts (Box 40, Folder 410)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Script and Storyboard for Slide Show (2 folders) (Box 40, Folder 411-412)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - NY Times Ad (Box 40, Folder 413)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Invitations, 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 414)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991 - Governing Magazine Ad (Box 40, Folder 415)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Special Report Intro, 1993 April (Box 40, Folder 416)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Version 3 Page Layout (Box 40, Folder 417)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Malcolm X, 1993 April (Box 40, Folder 418)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Manuscript, 1993 April (Box 40, Folder 419)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Pink Collar Ghetto, 1993 April (Box 40, Folder 420)
  - Spring Report 1993 - West African Museums Programme (WAMP) (Box 40, Folder 421)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Indonesia, 1993 April (Box 40, Folder 422)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Guadalupe, 1993 April (Box 40, Folder 423)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Briefly Noted, 1993 April (Box 40, Folder 424)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Draft (Box 41, Folder 425)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Draft, 1993 May (Box 41, Folder 426)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Covers, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 427)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Final Pages, 1993 April (Box 41, Folder 428)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Recent Grants, 1993 April (Box 41, Folder 429)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Approved Text Ready for Proofreader (Box 41, Folder 430)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Grants List Manuscript - Ready for Proofreader, 1993 March (Box 41, Folder 431)
  - Spring Report 1993 - Grants List Manuscript with Typesetting Marks, 1993 April (Box 41, Folder 432)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Typesetting Draft, 1993 May (Box 41, Folder 433)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Intro Special Report, 1993 August (Box 41, Folder 434)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Proofreader Notes (3 folders), 1993 July (Box 41, Folder 435-436, Box 42, Folder 437)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Quasar: Work in Progress - Draft, 1993 July (Box 42, Folder 438)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Memorial/Human Rights Group - Typesetting, 1993 July (Box 42, Folder 439)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Federal Employment Service - Proofs, 1993 July (Box 42, Folder 440)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Democracy After Communism/Stefan Batory, 1993 July (Box 42, Folder 441)
  - Summer Report 1993 - SOS Foundation, 1993 July (Box 42, Folder 442)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Women's Program Forum - Women in Politics, 1993 July (Box 42, Folder 443)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Briefly Noted, 1993 July (Box 42, Folder 444)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Recent Grants, 1993 July (Box 42, Folder 445)
  - Summer Report 1993 - Covers (Box 42, Folder 446)
  - Fall Report 1993 (8 folders), 1993 October (Box 42, Folder 447-449, Box 43, Folder 450-454)
    Proofs
  - Winter Report 1993 - Proofs, 1994 January (Box 44, Folder 455)
  - Winter Report 1993 - Cover, Ad, Contents, 1995 December (Box 44, Folder 456)
  - Winter Report 1993 - Michigan's Upper Peninsula, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 457)
  - Winter Report 1993 - MALDEF, 1994 January (Box 44, Folder 458)
  - Winter Report 1993 - China, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 459)
  - Winter Report 1993 - China Selects - Photos, 1993 November (Box 44, Folder 460)
  - Winter Report 1993 - Photos Selected - China Photo Novella, 1993 May-November (Box 44, Folder 461)
  - Winter Report 1993 - American Social History, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 462)
  - Winter Report 1993 - Briefly Noted, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 463)
  - Winter Report 1993 - Recent Grants, 1993 December-1994 January (Box 44, Folder 464)
  - Winter Report 1993 - Clippings File (Box 44, Folder 465)
  - 1999 Annual Report Corrections (from Field Offices), 2000 March (Box 44, Folder 466)
  - 1999 Annual Report - Corrections and Corrections Correspondence, 2000 March (Box 45, Folder 467)
  - 1999 Annual Report - Miscellaneous Memos, 1999 November-2000 January (Box 45, Folder 468)
  - Annual Report - Grants List - Notes/Memos/Email, 1998 November-1999 March (Box 45, Folder 469)
  - 1999 Annual Report - Suggestions, Photo Recommendations, Copies of Grant Action Documents (5 folders), 1999 August-September (Box 45, Folder 470-474)
  - 1999 Annual Report - Mission Statements - Oversize Proofs, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 475)
  - 1999 Annual Report - Mission Statements - Oversize Proofs, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 476)
  - Current Interests 1994 - Mockups and Quotes, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 477)
  - Current Interests 1994 - Quotes (Box 48, Folder 478)
  - Current Interests 1994 - Proofs (4 folders) (Box 48, Folder 479-482)
  - Current Interests 1994-1995 - Proofs (5 folders), 1994 May-September (Box 48, Folder 483, Box 49, Folder 484-487)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1990 - Slideshow (Box 49, Folder 488)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1993 (4 folders) (Box 49, Folder 489-491, Box 50, Folder 492)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1993 - Corrections (Box 50, Folder 493)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1993 - Schedules (Box 50, Folder 494)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1993 - Covers, 1992-1993 (Box 50, Folder 495)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1993 - Invitations (Box 50, Folder 496)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1993 - Brochure (Box 50, Folder 497)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1993 - Photo Selects (Box 50, Folder 498)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 - Folios - Corrected Pages (Box 50, Folder 499)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 - Posters, 1994 August-September (Box 50, Folder 500)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 - Posters - Memos and Printing Instructions, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 501)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 - Ads and Layouts (3 folders), 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 502-504)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 - Ad - Invitations, 1994 June-July (Box 51, Folder 505)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 - Schedules, 1994 May (Box 51, Folder 506)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 - Ads - Memos, 1994 June-September (Box 51, Folder 507)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1994 - Posters (Box 51, Folder 508)
  - Innovations in American Government 1995 - Proofs (Box 51, Folder 509)
  - Innovations in American Government 1997 - Building Trust (Box 51, Folder 510)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1988: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (Box 51, Folder 511)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1987: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (Box 51, Folder 512)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1986: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (Box 51, Folder 513)
  - Innovations in American Government 1998 - Achieving Excellence, Building Trust: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (Box 51, Folder 514)
  - Innovations in American Government: Creative Solutions to Public Concerns 2000: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University, In Partnership with the Council for Excellence in Government (Box 51, Folder 515)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1991: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (Box 51, Folder 516)
  - Innovations in American Government 1999: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University in Partnership with the Council for Excellence in Government (Box 51, Folder 517)
  - Innovations in State and Local Government 1990: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (Box 51, Folder 518)
  - Innovations in American Government: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University, 1986-1996 Tenth Anniversary (Box 51, Folder 519)
  - Innovations in American Government: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 520)
  - Innovating America: Innovations in State and Local Government: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation and John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, Fred Jordan, 1990 July (Box 51, Folder 521)
  - 1992 Innovations in State and Local Government: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation in Collaboration with the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (Box 51, Folder 522)
  - 1993 Innovations in State and Local Government: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation Administered by the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (Box 51, Folder 523)
  - 1994 Innovations in State and Local Government: An Awards Program of the Ford Foundation Administered by the John F. Kennedy School of Government at Harvard University (Box 51, Folder 524)
  - Ford Foundation at a Glance: Asset Building and Community Development, Peace and Social Justice, and Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 525)
  - Ford Foundation - Delivering on a Promise to Advance Human Welfare, 70 Years Timeline Pamphlet, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 526)
  - Captain Condom and Lady Latex: At War with the Army of Sex Diseases; Highlights of 25 Years of Youth Sexual and Reproductive Health Programming, 1991; 2003 (Box 51, Folder 527)
  - The Rituals and Practices of Slum/Shack Dwellers International, undated (Box 52, Folder 528)
  - NGO Accountability: Politics, Principles, and Innovations, Edited by Lisa Jordan and Peter Van Tuijl, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 529)
- Photographs, 1968-1993; 2; 1.75 Cubic Feet 5 containers
  Photographs separated from the Publications - Working Files by Ford Foundation staff prior to RAC acquisition. Originally accessioned as part of 2017:084.
  - American Dance Festival - Photos: Jay Anderson, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 219)
  - Cornfield and Corn Mesa, Zuni Pueblo, New Mexico - Photos: Stephen Trimble, undated (Box 25, Folder 220)
  - Scenes From the Play "August 29", undated (Box 25, Folder 221)
  - Museum of Anthropology, History and Art of the University of Puerto Rico, Workshop: Ceramic Technique of the Taino Indians, Museum Day, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 222)
  - Black Traditions "Song of the Disinherited" - Photos: Jay Anderson, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 223)
  - El Museo Del Barrio - "Emblems of His City: Jose Campeche and San Juan, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 224)
  - Cuban Museum of Arts and Culture - Exhibition: Cundo Bermudez and Reopening Ceremony, 1990 December 18 (Box 25, Folder 225)
  - Angkor Dance Troupe, 1991 January 8 (Box 25, Folder 226)
  - Museo Universidad de Puerto Rico Recinto de Rio Piedras, 1991 February 13 (Box 25, Folder 227)
    Museum of Anthropology, History and Art of the University of Puerto Rico, II Ceramic Bienial
  - The Mexican Museum, 1991 February 11 (Box 25, Folder 228)
  - President's Review: Women, Development, and Reproductive Health: A New Vision - Annual Report 1992, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 229)
  - Publications Catalogue, 1993 May-June (Box 25, Folder 230)
  - Ford Foundation Titles.ASC; Subject.ASC - ACII Files for Indexes to Catalog of Publications, Revised, 1993 June 28; 5.25 floppy disk - Macintosh (Box 25, Folder 230)
  - ASCII File for Index to 1992 Annual Report (Box 25, Folder 231)
  - Ford Foundation - Ford92.ASC ASCII File for Index to 1992 Annual Report, One 3.5" floppy and one 5.25" floppy (Box 25, Folder 231)
  - Annual Reports Covers, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 232)
    Includes photographs of the Ballet Hispanico
  - #53824 P. 1-4 Negatives, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 233)
  - #52960 P. 1 and P. 5, #54631 P. 1, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7 Negatives, undated (Box 25, Folder 234)
  - #53824 P. 7 - V. Englebert/Black Star (11-83-6356) Yanomami Indians, Amazon - Brazil, circa 1983 (Box 25, Folder 235)
  - #53824 P. 7 - V. Englebert/Black Star (11-83-6356) Yanomami Indians, Amazon - Brazil, circa 1983 (Box 25, Folder 236)
  - #53824 P-3 C.S. Perkins/Magnum (D90-117/32) Yanomami Indians, Brazil - Sheltered from the Rain Under a Banana Leaf, undated (Box 25, Folder 237)
  - #54631 P3 - J. Kyle Keener - Philadelphia Inquirer - Matrix - Brazil, Amazon 8911D, Rain Forest - Rondonia Squatters, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 238)
  - #52960-5 - V. Englebert Blackstar F-2412 Yanomami Indians #9, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 239)
  - #54631 P.1 - Peter Jordan, Network Matrix, Poland Pollution, Nowy Bytom 9000D, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 240)
  - #54631 P7 - No. 4 - 168.324 - Amazon, Brazil, Photo: Laif - Sipa-Press, P41a, 1988 December (Box 25, Folder 241)
  - #54631 P5 No. 2: 164.574 - Bresil, Destruction of Forests - PH: F4/R. Azoury - AF309, Sipa-Press, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 242)
  - #54631-P4 - 164.594 - Bresil, Destrution Des Forets - Photo: F4/Benedicto - Sipa-Press, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 243)
  - #52960 P2 - C.S. Perkins/Magnum - Yanomami Indians - 090p0117/04 - Family Portrait, undated (Box 25, Folder 244)
    Indians with more contact with West adopt clothing but keep beliefs
  - #53186 C2-3 - Social Forestry - India, undated (Box 25, Folder 245)
  - #48178 - G. Henoch/Gamma Liaison, undated (Box 25, Folder 246)
  - #54291 P1 - 193.744 - Moscou, Penurie de Pommes de Terre - Photo: Laski/Sipa Press, 1990 October (Box 25, Folder 247)
  - #54291 P4 - 195.891 - Moscou: Penuries - Photo: Laski/Sipa Press - No. 4, 1990 November (Box 25, Folder 248)
  - #54291 P3 U.R.S.S. - 196555 - Penurie de Pain a Moscou - Photo: Laski/Sipa Press - 192.347, 1990 September (Box 25, Folder 249)
  - #54291 P2 - 542/Moscou - Penurie de Pain - Photo: Laski/Sipa Press, 1990 September (Box 25, Folder 250)
  - #54291 P1-4 (Negatives), undated (Box 25, Folder 251)
  - #54755 P1, P2 (Negative); P1 (Positive), undated (Box 25, Folder 252)
  - #52960 P6 - Memphis, Tennessee, Mississippi River - Photo Researchers, Inc. - 55 0709 - Ray Ellis, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 253)
  - #52960 P1 - Andrew Sacks, Blackstar - 2-88-0512 - Detroit, Michigan Skyline, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 254)
  - #54631 P2 (Positive and Negative); #52960 - P1, 3, 4, 6, 7, 8, 9 (Negative), P1-9 (Positive), undated (Box 25, Folder 255)
  - Population - Nigerian Association of University Women (Photos) - For Annual Report 1990 (Box 25, Folder 256)
    "Graduation ceremony" of the training courses in family planning and basic health education - Grant no. 905 0441
  - #45957 P1, 2, 3, 4 (Negative), undated (Box 25, Folder 257)
  - P1, undated (Box 25, Folder 258)
  - P2, undated (Box 25, Folder 259)
  - P3, undated (Box 25, Folder 260)
  - 1979 Annual Report Photos - 44337-4 (Box 25, Folder 261)
  - 1977 Annual Report Photos, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 262)
  - 1969 Annual Report Photos (Box 26, Folder 263-264)
  - 1968 Annual Report Photos (Box 26, Folder 265)
  - 1988 Annual Report Photos - Human Rights and Social Justice Photos (Box 26, Folder 266)
  - 1988 Annual Report Photos - Governance and Public Policy (Box 26, Folder 267)
  - 1988 Annual Report Photos - Rural Poverty Alternate (Box 26, Folder 268)
  - 1988 Annual Report - International Affairs (Box 26, Folder 269)
  - Expertype - Work Order #10564 - Job Name: Wang-ASCII, 1989 May 4; 5 1/4 inch floppy disk (Box 26, Folder 269)
  - Ford Text, Urban Poverty, Rural Poverty, undated; 5 1/4 inch floppy disk (Box 26, Folder 269)
  - Expertype, Inc., 10526, Wang to ASCII - File: Exper. All, 1989 May 3; 5 1/4 inch floppy disk (Box 26, Folder 269)
  - 1988 Annual Report (Box 26, Folder 270)
  - 1989 Photo Research (Box 26, Folder 271)
  - Job #12898 1989 Annual Report Photos (Box 26, Folder 272)
  - Disk 0177T - Duplicate - Ford Foundation Annual Report Manuscript - Text/PRI - 4978T - International Affairs - 5102T - 38329, 1989; 8 inch floppy disk (Box 26, Folder 272)
  - 38329 Annual Report 1989 (Box 27, Folder 273)
  - 38329 Annual Report 1990 (Box 27, Folder 274)
  - 38329 1991 Annual Report Photos (Box 27, Folder 275-276)
  - Freeland 3.0 - Ford Foundation Annual Report Charts, 1992 March 3; 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 27, Folder 276)